

SLIL PUANGPOOM

Senior Software Engineer

THANK YOU FOR VISITING

https://www.blink-me-code.dev

ABOUT ME

I have 4+ years experienced in web development especially on frontend with React.js / Next.js and passionate in full stack so I learn Node.js / Nest.js and other new technology more than in my official job . You can see more about my information in my own website.



slil.puangpoom@gmail.com



087-500-6783



Bangkok, Bangsue, 10800

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering Industrial Engineering Chulalongkorn University

2013-05 / 2017-07

EXPERIENCE

Ascend Group (Ascend Bit) 2022-07 / Present Senior Software Engineer (Frontend)

- Blockchain projects (wallet /point / loyalty program)
- Design system with storybook
- Web3, DApp

Refinitiv An LESG Business 2021-07 / 2022-06 Software Engineer (Frontend)

- Data platform project
- Building enterprise grade web application
- Working with international teams
- Agile software development

Hatari wireless Software Engineer

2018-10 / 2021-06

- Software house with variety type of projects
- Work as Fullstack developer with startup culture
- React / C# .Net Core / AWS

EXPERTISE

- React / Next.js
- JavaScript / TypeScript
- MUI / Tailwind / Bootstrap
- Redux / Jest / Web3

OPEN TO WORK

- Node.js /Nest.js
- MongoDB / MySQL / PostgreSQL